Hey, Ruben, congratulations. Uh, I don't
know where you expected to go in terms
of the first round. Can you just give us
your reaction about the Buccaneers
taking you and and remaining in the
state of Florida?
>> Uh, such a relief, man, knowing that I
was fortunate enough to get my name
called tonight, no matter where it was.
Uh, having my name having my name called
been a dream for the last 17 years. And
so, actually having seeing this and
hearing it come true, it's it's a it's a
great feeling. and just the cherry on
top of staying in Florida, man. I have
family members that stay in uh Tampa. I
have um former cousins that play for uh
the Bucks. So, it's it's going to be a
familiar atmosphere for me. Um and I'm
just excited and stoked to get there.
>> Who are your cousins that played for the
Bucks?
>> Carlton Davis.
>> Boss. Yeah. Recent recent history.
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> Did you hear from Carlton after you got
picked? Uh my phone's on D and D right
now, so I know once I [laughter] get
here, uh I'll be able to I'll be able to
probably hear from you.
>> You're gonna have to update us on how
many messages you had once you finally
get back to it. That's
>> a lot.
>> Hey, Ruben, what kind of interaction did
you have with the draft with the Bucks
during the draft process?
>> Um I'll be honest, not a lot, but uh the
ones I had, he wor um I told him, man,
like I got family that stay in Temple,
so it's going to be easy for me. It's
going to be easy to transition. So let's
do it. and coach Bulls did it.
>> What do you know about Bull's defense
and how do you think you're going to fit
into it?
>> I feel like I fit in just fine. Um coach
Coach Bulls is an aggressive defensive
like-minded coach and I'm an aggressive
defensive like-minded player. So I feel
like it's it's two and two put together.
It's going to be real simple, real
smooth. Now it's just about me learning
plays, earning the trust of my teammates
and learning what I can do to help the
team.
>> Kasha Kansas is from Miami. Do you do
you know him? Have you?
>> Yeah, real well. Real well. So, I know I
know when I get him on my phone, it's
going to be it's going to be a great
conversation.
>> What have the last couple weeks been
like for you? Because you've had all
this training and and buildup and then
obviously the news surfaced a couple
weeks ago about the accident in 2024.
Like, how how did you kind of handle all
that? How did you navigate that? I'm
sure there's a lot of emotional highs
and lows that that really go into that.
And then leading up to this moment,
>> uh, yeah, you know, everything has it
ups and downs, but I I I just try to
make everything simple as it could
possibly be. Um, try to prioritize
whatever I prioritize in the moment. And
right now, that's is uh just football
and and making sure I'm just really
making as a main priority for me. Um, my
days are kind of fairly simple. Just
working out, going home, getting on the
phone, and pretty much doing the same
thing. And it's been a rinse and repeat
kind of cycle.
Ruben, when it comes to football, what
would you say is your best trait in
terms of what you bring on the field and
also maybe in the locker room?
>> My motive, I feel like my motor and my
mindset is contagious cuz when people
see me, how I play and how I care about
the game of football kind of spreads off
on other people and I actually have
proof of that and that's not me just
talking. That's from high school all the
way up into college.
>> How did working with Jason Taylor at the
U prepare you to play at this next
level?
>> Can you repeat that one more time,
please?
working with Jason Taylor, how did that
prepare you to play at the next level?
>> I felt like I got the best the best
coaching I could possibly get these last
three years. I mean, it's Hall of Fame
coaching. I don't really realize until I
look back on it or hear somebody else
talking about it. Um, so now it's just a
amazing opportunity and I was blessed
enough to get that that style of play,
that style of coaching for the last
three years. And not too many people can
say they had one position coach all the
whole college career and mine was a Hall
of Famer. So, it's just even more
cherries on top.
>> Well, I mean, in so much of our
pre-draft, like leadup as media members,
we're talking about you and we're
talking about your teammate Hakee Meador
because both of you guys I mean, it's
rare to have two guys, you know, at the
same position in in one draft class that
are both being talked about as as
potential first round picks.
>> Oh yeah, man. It's very rare, but we
did, man. That's a credit to us. That's
a credit to coach Chris Paul, coach
Taylor and and how we came about our
work each and every day on the green
tree whether I was in any stadium home
all way. We care about football so much
and I feel like you seen it in our play
and and God just had the results that
that came out tonight.
>> What was the feeling like to walk across
the stage, meet the commissioner, hear
your name called in Pittsburgh. What was
that feeling emotion like for you?
>> It was awesome. U something I dreamed
of, like I said, for the last 17 years
of my life. So, actually getting to
actually getting to go through with it.
Um, it was amazing. Not too many people
get invited to the draft. Uh, so it
wasn't I took it wasn't something I took
for grinning. Every every second I was
here, I love them because I knew there'd
be people be that's dying to be in my
seat right now.
>> And I heard your family has coordinated
outfits. How did that all come about?
>> Uh, it's just idea I came up with. Um,
we kind of was able and fortunate enough
to kind of pull it off and I feel like
we all look coordinated and smooth.
>> Oh yeah.
>> How much has your family support meant
to you throughout this trip? A
>> lot. It means the world to me. I have
about 20 to 25 family members up here
today. Um, and five of those stay in
Tampa. So, I know I have a a great
support system that's going to be there.
So, anybody I need to lean on, they're
automatically there. Then my family's
only three hours away. So, it's nothing
but a days of road trip.
>> What do you want fans to know about the
player and the person that they're going
to be getting?
>> That I love football and whoever my
teammates. I love my teammates. Hing up
my teammates. I hate them. This is what
[laughter] I This is what I This is what
I love to do. And I'm a buck, so I love
to be a buck.
>> Are there any Buccaneers players over
the years that you've watched at all and
admired?
>> Um, Elijah uh um cuz he from Miami, he
did it such a high level, especially
that crazy rookie year he had. Uh and um
I feel like everybody knows Tom Brady
because Tom Brady um Mike Evans because
what he do is Mike Evans. Um it's just
I've been fortunate enough to know
people. Um, like I say, my cousin Clark
and Levante David, he's been there for a
long time. So, I'll be able to get on
the phone with him after this and just
get the best uh I feel like opinion and
best review.
>> So, so that's a name that you need to
drop around here very very frequently.
Leavante David. He's he's very well
thought of and
>> you talk to Sav.
He was actually just at the spring game.
So, I know you're gonna have something
to say when you see me. [laughter]
>> Anything else? Congratulations, Ruben.
Congratulations, Ruben. Y'all have a
good night.